mystore411.com 2018-01-31

# View store locations, hours, maps, phone numbers, services and more

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices of this site. Specifically, it outlines the types of information that we gather about you while you are using the site, and the ways in which we use and share this information.

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

If you visit the Website, we do not collect any personally identifiable information about you (such as your name, address, phone number or email address) unless you provide it. You may provide personal information in order to contact us or report of an error. We use the personal information you provide us solely for the purpose of communicating back to you. We will not disclose any personal information to a third party without your express prior written authorization. 

## Log Files

Mystore411 automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, date and time of access, browser type, platform type, referring url, and the page you request. This information does not identify you personally and is used in an aggregate way to help us improve our web site and tell us how many people visit our site over a period of time. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer. For example, a web site may use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you, your preferences, or the pages you last visited.

We do not use cookies to store or collect information on our web site.

However, some of our business partners use cookies on our site. We use third-party advertising companies (such as Google) to serve ads when you visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/). 

## Links to Other Sites

This site includes links to external web sites. We encourage users to review the privacy policy of each linked site, as we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. 

## Contact Information

If you have questions or suggestions about our privacy policy, please contact us.
